♪ Come to me, pretty ♪
♪ Pull back my limbs ♪
♪ It's the oldest tradition ♪
♪ Known to my skin ♪
♪ I can be soft ♪
♪ When I'm disarmed ♪
♪ I can be just ♪
♪ What you want. ♪
食肉就是谋杀
萨维奇河/野人河
第一季第一集
是她的生日吗
Is it her birthday?
不，这更像是一个，呃......
No, this is more of a, uh...
不，这更像是一个欢迎回家的蛋糕，亲爱的
No, this is more ..a welcome-home cake, honey.
她和你一样有胡子吗
Does she have a beard like you?
胡子
A beard?
我是说，我...
I mean, I...
宝贝，我甚至没有胡子 看
Baby, I don't even have a beard. Look.
你有胡须
Baby, I don't even have a beard. You have whiskers.
呸 它是多刺的 你有胡须
Grr! It's prickly. You have whiskers.
那伤害了吗
Grr! It's prickly. Did that hurt?
我觉得它很尖
I feel like it's spiky.
我觉得它很尖 不，我们不是……我们不相同
I feel like it's spiky. No, we're not...we're not identical.
异卵双胞胎 看
Fraternal twins. See?
还记得那是什么意思吗
Remember what that means?
贾米拉，在那之后
Jamila, after that
你可以在后面整理一些其他的盒子
you could sort some of the other boxes out the back.
嗯
Mm?
你知道，如果你愿意，你可以拥有那个
You know, you can have that one if you like.
你知道，你可以拥有那个哦 不
You know, you can have that one Oh. No!
不 你可以 把它带回家
No! You can. Take it home.
哦，谢谢
Oh, thank you.
- 没关系……  - 早上好
- It's alright... - Morning!
哦 你好
Ooh! Hello.
你好 早安，贾米拉
Hi. Morning, Jamila.
介意我借你的窗户...
Mind if I borrow your window...
..几个星期
..for a couple of weeks?
不，只是... 直到选举
No. Just... Just till the election?
是啊 好吧，好吧，不，对你好
Yeah.... Yeah. Alright, well, no, good on you
举起你的手 对，在这儿
for putting your hand up. Yep, over here?
哦，很好 帮我一把，科琳
Oh, good. Give me a hand, Colleen.
干得好
Here you go.
这是一个好地方 嗯 嗯
This is a good spot. Mm-hm.
这是一个好地方 好，我们上去
This is a good spot. Alright, up we go.
正确的 哦，它是巨大的
Right. Oh, it's huge!
你觉得够大吗
You think it's big enough?
好的，在上面吗
Alright, up here?
是的 是的，我认为这很好
Yeah. Yeah, I think that's good.
好的，我们会在这里录下来
Alright, we'll tape it up here.
适合 完美的
Fits. Perfect.
科琳? 你还好吗
Colleen? Are you alright?
不，我很好 我，嗯...
No, I'm fine. I, um...
我要为你投票 绝对地
I'm gonna be voting for you. Absolutely.
我要为你投票 好吧，那是一票反对
I'm gonna be voting for you. Well, that's one vote down.
只有2000人去
Only 2,000 to go.
多一点磁带，我想，亲爱的
A bit more tape, I think, darl'.
嘿
Hey.
哦，该死的地狱
Oh, bloody hell!
哦，天呐
Oh, Jesus.
哇
Wow.
我不敢相信你真的在这里
I can't believe you're really here.
呃……这是你的米基阿姨
Uh... This is your Aunty Miki.
你一定是……河
You must be...River.
不，不，湖，是吗
No. No. Lake, is it?
嗯
Hm?
我知道 是海洋
I know. It's Ocean.
很适合你
It suits you.
哦，是的，进来吧 我去拿你的东西
Oh, yeah, come in. I'll grab your stuff.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
看看我们做了什么
Look what we made.
是的，呃……嗯……
Yeah, uh... Well...
是谁干的，嗯 我们这样做了吗
Who did that, huh? Did we do that?
给米基阿姨
For Aunty Miki?
嘿，你应该有，嗯...
Hey, you should have, um...
你应该打电话的 嘿，你应该有，嗯...
You should have called. Hey, you should have, um...
我已经准备好来接你了
You should have called. I was all set to pick you up.
我没有电话
You should have called. I don't have a phone.
我们现在可以做糖衣了吗
Can we make the icing now?
很好的混合，宝贝 做得好
Good mixing there, baby. Well done.
好的，现在，有多少粉红色的 我们把它们算出来了吗
Alright, now, how many pink ones? Have we counted them out?
我可以做洒水吗
Alright, now, how many pink ones? Can I do the sprinkles?
我是来收拾床铺的 对不起，米基
I meant to make up the bed! Sorry, Miki!
- 我们赢了  - 我很高兴
- We won!  - I'm so glad.
恭喜，姑娘们 这太棒了
Congratulations, girls. That was awesome!
恭喜，姑娘们 谢谢你，恩格勒特先生
Congratulations, girls. Thank you, Mr Englert!
停止
Stop!
你在写什么
What are you writing?
没有什么
Nothing.
好的
OK.
你答应和我做朋友吗
Do you promise to still be friends with me
你答应我什么时候，像，无聊和老
Do you promise when I'm, like, boring and old?
你没说承诺 哦 好的 我保证
You didn't say promise! Oh! OK! I promise!
你没说承诺 我保证 我保证
You didn't say promise! I promise! I promise.
好的
OK.
不像你和科琳，是吗
Not like you and Colleen, is it?
这样选边站
Taking sides like this?
黛博拉有一些好主意
Deborah has some good ideas.
格林尼胡说八道
Greenie panic-mongering nonsense.
她会关闭肉类加工厂
She'll shut the meatworks down.
那么这个小镇会在哪里呢
Then where will this town be?
我想她想把它清理干净，那么这个小镇会在哪里
I think she wants to clean it up, Then where will this town be?
我想她想清理它，而不是关闭它
I think she wants to clean it up, not shut it down.
清理河流，适当支付人
Clean up the river, pay people properly.
清理河流，用什么
Clean up the river, With what?
金钱树上的钱
Money from the money tree?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我们现在该走了
We should go now.
我会带着我自己的海报回来
I'll be back with a poster of my own.
我会回来只是为了公平
I'll be back Just to be fair.
刚才那是干什么啊
What was that all about?
典型的麦克斯不喜欢它 想要他自己的海报
Typical Max didn't like it. Wants his own poster up.
典型的麦克斯不喜欢它 公平地说，我没有意识到...
Typical Max didn't like it. To be fair, I didn't realise...
嘘
Boo!
爸爸
Daddy!
- 这是给我的 这是给我的  - 呃...
- It's for me! It's for me!  - Uh...
这是给我的 这是给我的 宝贝，等等，我应该...
It's for me! It's for me! Baby, wait, I should...
我会得到它
I'll get it.
你好，亲爱的 你父亲在家吗
Hello, sweetheart. Is your father home?
进来吧哦
Come in. Oh!
进来谢谢
Come in. Thank you.
呃……科琳，如果你，嗯……
Uh... Colleen, if you, um...
很抱歉，但我... 我认为现在真的很糟糕
I'm sorry, but I... I think this is really bad time.
对不起，但我……不，我们……我们不会待太久，特里
I'm sorry, but I... No, we...we won't stay long, Terry.
请
Please.
你好，米基
Hello, Miki.
哦，你看起来不错
Oh, you look well.
也许我们应该稍后再回来
Maybe we should come back later.
休，我们同意了
Hugh, we agreed.
我们认为您可能只需要一些东西 嗯...
We thought you just might need a few things. Um...
不知道这些天你会穿什么
Didn't know what you'd be wearing these days.
科琳，你不必这样做 不好了
Colleen, you don't have to do this. Oh, no.
科琳，你不必这样做 是的，我们有
Colleen, you don't have to do this. Yes, we do.
很抱歉我们没有早点来看你
I'm sorry we didn't come to see you sooner.
她不希望我们在这里
She doesn't want us here.
不，我...
No, I...
我想我只是……不习惯访客
I guess I'm just... not used to visitors.
你知道，不是没有一周的通知和完整的腔搜索
You know, not without a week's notice and a full cavity search.
我们只想说...
All we wanted to say was...
..我们原谅你
..we forgive you.
为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
看起来井井有条
Looks in order.
我们会有一个双重间谍，嗯...
We'll have a Double Agent, um...
..柳树和...罗马蜡烛 还有什么
..Willows and...Roman Candles. What else?
他不是要库存，尼克
He's not asking for an inventory, Nick.
我们在时代广场庆祝 Savage River，而不是跨年夜
We're celebrating Savage River, not New Year's Eve in Times Square.
别担心，比尔，这将是史诗般的
Don't worry, Bill, it's gonna be epic.
别担心，比尔，它会看起来很棒
Don't worry, Bill, It's gonna look awesome.
来吧
Come on.
嘿
Hey.
米基
Miki!
我……来签到
I'm...here to sign in.
知道你要来的一件事，
One thing knowing you're coming,
又一次见到你的肉体
quite another seeing you again in the flesh.
你和你哥哥住在一起吗
You ARE staying with your brother?
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
找到了工作
Got a job?
还没有
Not yet.
当你得到一个时告诉我
Let me know when you get one.
每周一次，直到您的假释结束
Once a week until your parole is up.
我会不时检查你
And I'll be checking in on you from time to time.
我只想过我的生活
I just want to live my life.
像其他人一样 就这些
Like everyone else. That's all.
就我而言，干净的石板
Clean slate, as far as I'm concerned.
这是你必须担心的镇上的其他地方
It's the rest of the town you have to worry about.
男：请给斯里兰卡200
MAN: 200 to Sri Lanka, please.
呃...这是接收器的详细信息
Uh... Here's the receiver details.
耶，好样的 就在那儿
Yeah, good. Just on there.
嗯...
Um...
我不需要每次都看你的身份证 我知道是你
I don't need to see your ID every time. I know it's you.
我不需要看你的ID 谢谢
I don't need to see your ID Thank you.
这一切都完成了
That's all done.
干得好 谢谢
Here you go. Thanks.
这么久了还在寄钱回家
Still sending money back home after all this time.
还在寄钱回家 你妈妈一定把你养大了
Still sending money back home Your mum must have raised you right.
是的，她做到了
Yeah, she did.
泰拉
Taylah?
呃...
Uh...
我们，嗯……九年级一起上学了
We, um...went to school together in Year 9.
你是，呃……哇
You're, uh... Wow.
是的 是的，还有六个星期
Yeah. Yeah, six weeks to go.
这是惊人的
That's amazing.
呃...
Uh...
倒霉 你是米基
Shit. You're Miki.
是的，呃......我们应该赶上一些时间
Yeah, uh...we should catch up some time.
嗯
Uh-huh.
是的
Yeah.
艾薇，请为肉类加工厂的急救箱准备一个盒子
Ivy, put a box together for the meatworks' first-aid kit, please.
常春藤，把一个盒子放在一起，我告诉他们我会把它放在那里
Ivy, put a box together for the I told them I'd drop it up there.
嘿
Hey.
你好 你有工作要去这里吗
Hi. Do you have a job going here?
你必须和柯比先生谈谈这件事
You have to talk to Mr Kirby about that.
你好 我可以帮你吗
Hi. Can I help you?
呃...是的，我只是在问销售助理的工作
Uh... Yeah, I was just asking about the sales assistant job.
你以前在化学家工作过吗
Have you ever worked in a chemist before?
好的 嗯...
OK. Um...
有参考吗 我可以打电话给谁
Got any references? Someone I can call?
呃……没关系 我只会得到这些
Uh... Never mind. I'll just get these.
好的
OK.
好的 好的
Good. Good?
好的 是的
Good. Yeah.
让它们保持六周
Keep them in for six weeks
并保持清洁
and keep them clean with this.
那么，只有耳环吗
So, just the earrings, then?
呃……是的
Uh... Yep.
呃……还有这些
Uh... And these.
还有避孕套
And the condoms?
好的
OK.
好吧，谁想要晚餐排骨
Alright, who wants chops for dinner?
我
Me!
还有炸薯条
And French fries too!
好的
Nice.
排骨
Chops?
呃……不，我出去的时候会得到一些东西
Uh... No, I'll get something when I'm out.
出去
Out?
在哪里
Where?
我要去酒吧看看
I'm gonna check out the pub.
这是你的第一个晚上 也许，呃……也许慢慢来
It's your first night. Maybe, uh... Maybe take it slow?
这是你的第一个晚上 你什么时候变得这么老了
It's your first night. When did you become such an old man?
不知道，你什么时候变得这么老了
I don't know, When did you become such an old man?
我不知道，也许当我有孩子的时候，找到了一份工作
I don't know, maybe when I had a kid, got a job.
我不知道，我也可以去吗
I don't know, Can I go too?
不
No.
金克斯
Jinx.
再见
See ya.
请问我可以和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you, please?
你想要什么
What do you want?
这个给你
This is for you.
应该对我有意义吗
Supposed to mean something to me?
这是贾斯的主意
It was Jas's idea.
她在电影里看过 它就像一个时间胶囊
She'd seen it in a movie. It's like a time capsule.
我们把它埋在后院
We buried it in the backyard.
看 这是，嗯...
See? This is, um...
如果你这样做......那就是柠檬树
If you do that... That's the lemon tree.
然后你就有了房子和栅栏
And then you've got the house and the fence.
然后你得到了我刚刚的房子...
And then you've got the house I just...
我只是想你可能想要它
I just thought you might want it.
你从我身边夺走了我的女儿
You took my daughter from me.
你觉得这能弥补吗
Think this is gonna make up for it?
我知道我不能改变...
I know I can't change...
像对待家人一样对待你，而你...
Treated you like part of the family, and you...
休，对不起，好吗 我……我很抱歉
Hugh, I'm sorry, OK? I... I'm so sorry.
休，对不起，好吗 出去
Hugh, I'm sorry, OK? Get out!
你怎么敢
How dare you?!
当她不能的时候，你怎么敢在你的肺里呼吸
How dare you take breath in your lungs when she can't?!
继续前进
And keep going!
休，来吧
Hugh, come on.
发生了什么
What happened?
♪ In the night I heard calling ♪
♪ I felt your curse But I know there is no sound ♪
♪ It woke me up when I was dreaming... ♪
♪ It woke me up Thanks, mate. ♪
♪ And I cut the rope But your ghost is still around... ♪
嘿
Hey!
西蒙
Simon!
你好
Hello?!
嘿
Hey.
听说你回来了
I heard you were back.
是的
Yeah?
是的 嗯...
Yeah. Um...
你知道，我……我想我会，嗯……
You know, I...I figured I'd, um...
..给你一个安定下来的机会，然后...
..just give you a chance to get settled and...
好的
OK.
嗯，嗯...
Well, um...
我以为你死了什么的
I thought you died or something.
是的，我，嗯...
Yeah, I, um...
我真的应该解释一下
I really should have explained.
我……我道歉
I... I apologise.
你道歉
You apologise?
我真的不知道还能说什么
I don't really know what else to say.
你是否厌倦了你的小监狱慈善项目
Did you get bored of your little prison-charity project?
是这样吗 事实并非如此
Is that it? That's not what happened.
你知道，我其实很期待见到你
You know, I actually looked forward to seeing you.
你知道，我实际上做了你要求我做的一切
You know, I actually I did everything you asked me to.
我读了所有的书 我... 我为考试而学习
I read all the books. I... I studied for my exams.
你告诉我我有未来 然后你就...
You told me I had a future, and then you just...
..停止来看我
..stopped coming to see me.
米基……不要
Miki... Don't!
米基……听着，我对你没有恶意
Miki... Look, I don't mean shit to you!
这很好
And that's fine.
好的 只要我们都清楚
OK? So long as we're both clear.
米基...
Miki...
没有为什么 每天 他是第一个进门的人
No, why? Every day? He's the first one through the door.
第一个进门，试图弄湿他的嘴唇
First one through the door, trying to get his lips wet.
托莫 托莫
Tommo! Tommo!
请给我们四品脱的饮料好吗
Can we get four pints of the draught, please?
- 我们可以买四品脱 - 当然，伙计
- Can we get four pints - Sure, mate.
草稿，是的 我想试试这个
Draught, yes. I want to try this one.
我不知道它是什么，但我想试试
I don't know what it is, but I want to try.
是的，你确实想尝试 是的
Yes, you DO want to try. Yes.
其实，嗯...
Actually, um...
对不起
Sorry.
好吧，至少你的举止正在改善
Well, at least your manners are improving.
什么
What?
我不会让外面的那些男孩看到你喝得这么醉
I wouldn't let those boys outside see you drunk like that.
我不会让那些男孩出去的
I wouldn't let those boys outside
为什么不
Why not?
你会让他们认为你不会大打出手
You'll have them thinking you won't put up much of a fight.
好吧...
Well, then...
..他们错了
..they'd be wrong.
你要去哪里
Where are You going?
该我请你喝酒吗
My shout?
让开，你这个无赖，否则我会告诉你怎么做的
Move over, you dickless one, or I'll show you how it's done.
让开，你这个没用的人，嗯。。。
Move over, you dickless one, Um...
当然 为什么不
Sure. Why not?
两杯或更多？当然 为什么不呢
Two more? Sure. Why not?
- 这要两杯  - 好的，伙计
- Two more?  - Righto, mate.
两杯或更多？ 顺便说一下，我是乔尔
Two more? I'm Joel, by the way.
我是米基
I'm Miki.
我知道
I know.
有人敢和镇上的杀手调情吗
Someone dare you to flirt with the town killer?
调情
Flirting?
这就是我在做的吗
Is that what I'm doing?
我怎么会知道
How would I know?
我最近只和监狱看守谈过
Only men I've spoken to in a while are prison guards.
我只跟我谈过的男人啊，是吗
Only men I've spoken to in a while Ah, yeah?
干杯
Cheers.
他们会调情吗
Are they good flirts?
厕所
Shithouse.
那就从我这里拿走吧
Well, take it from me then -
我是萨维奇河最好的调情者
I'm the best flirt in all of Savage River.
我知道你会微笑
I knew you could smile.
我希望有一顿免费的饭菜
I was hoping for a free meal.
对不起爸爸 你只能靠自己 我有英语课
Sorry, Dad. You're on your own. I've got English lessons.
不能依赖这个镇上的任何人
Can't rely on anyone in this town.
你能相信黛博拉吗 现在贴海报
Can you believe Deborah? Putting up posters now?
我还没有时间自己打印
I haven't had time to get my own printed.
你已经有点自满了
You have been getting a little complacent.
你明白了，她认为她更聪明 比我强
You have been getting She thinks she's smarter than I am.
过来
Come here.
你怎么看
What do you reckon?
呃...
Uh...
它...
It...
这些是什么时候的了
How old are these?
没那么老
Not that old.
归根结底，它们将符合目的
End of the day, they'll fit the purpose.
是的 绝对地
Yeah. Absolutely.
好吧，我们可能会度过一个晚上
Well, we might make a night of it.
把整个该死的小镇涂在他们身上
Plaster the whole bloody town in them.
爸爸，我刚刚告诉过你我今晚有英语课
Dad, I just told you I've got English lessons tonight.
他们需要英语做什么 他们只是在割羊
What do they need English for? They're just cutting up sheep.
他们需要英语做什么
What do they need English for?
我以为你想让外国人同化
I thought you wanted the foreigners to assimilate.
你应该出去和某个年轻女人谈恋爱
You should be out romancing some young woman.
你应该出去 好吧
You should be out Alright.
我会……明天帮你
I'll...help you tomorrow.
好的
OK?
也许我只会在她的胡子上画胡子
Maybe I'll just draw moustaches on hers instead.
也许我会
Maybe I'll just
你会的，不是吗
You would, wouldn't you?
你会的，不是吗 来吧
You would, wouldn't you? Come on.
疯子 走着瞧
Lunatic. We'll see.
疯子
Lunatic.
给我们一点时间
Give us a sec.
这让人放心
That's reassuring.
我是肉类加工厂的屠夫
I'm a...slaughterman at the meatworks.
这就是你不怕我的原因吗
Is that why you're not afraid of me?
我绝对害怕你
I'm absolutely terrified of you.
我在伤害你吗
Am I hurting you?
你应该这样做，不是吗
You're supposed to, aren't you?
嗯...
Um...
这是你的第一次
It's your first time.
嗯...
Um...
糟糕 呃...
Shit. Uh...
对不起 我没有意识到
Sorry. I didn't realise.
生气
Piss off.
你不必去
You don't have to go.
我们完成了，对吧
We're done, right?
我不再是处女了
I'm not a virgin anymore.
正确的
Right.
所以，你喝醉了，发生了性关系
So, you got drunk, had sex.
接下来是什么 所以，你喝醉了，发生了性关系
What's next? So, you got drunk, had sex.
接下来是什么 拿到驾照，撞车
What's next? Get your licence, crash a car?
是的
Yeah.
也许
Maybe.
只是...
Just...
..等等，我送你回家
..hang on, I'll give you a lift home.
..等等，我很好
..hang on, I'm fine.
我说我很好
I said I'm fine.
你好，亲爱的
给你这个 我想你可能会喜欢它
你一直在喝酒
我记得这种颜色曾经很适合你
我们的儿子已经死了
亲爱的阿里走了
你转身就去喝酒
这就是安拉对我们失望的原因
并且不会给我们第二个孩子
现在我姐姐也走了
我们都做出了选择
莱拉做了她的选择
嘿
Hey.
兴奋剂检测 记得吗
Drug test. Remember?
哦 是的 废话
Oh. Yeah. Shit.
你应该是，嗯...
Should you be, um...
..这样做
..doing that?
这些天我有一个很好的理由来控制它
I've got a pretty good reason to keep it under control these days.
合同法案例研究
Contract law case studies.
是的，我，呃......我有点喜欢它 这……这很奇怪
Yeah, I'm, uh... I'm kind of into it. It's... It's weird.
是的，我是，呃......我有点你是个他妈的怪人
Yeah, I'm, uh... I'm kind of You're a fucking weirdo.
嗯
Mm.
这是计划吗，米基
Is this the plan then, Miki?
深夜进来，醉了
Come in late at night, drunk.
进入人们的脸上
Get in people's faces.
看，我会找到工作的 好的
Look, I'll get a job. OK?
我会帮助你解决海洋问题
I'll help you out with Ocean.
如果她真的跟我说话
If she ever actually speaks to me.
这就是我想要的 好的
That's all I want. OK?
就是在这里和你们两个这就是我想要的 好的
Is to be here with you two That's all I want. OK?
就是在这里和你们两个一起做正常的事情
Is to be here with you two just doing normal shit.
说到正常的事，我给你买了一部手机
Speaking of normal shit, I bought you a phone.
什么 是的
What? Yeah.
你能用这个东西追踪我的一举一动吗
Can you, like, trace my every move with this thing?
哦耶 是的 我也能听到你所有的谈话，所以要小心
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I can hear all your conversations too, so be careful.
你是认真的 哦，你这个白痴
Are you serious? Oh, you idiot.
哦...
Ohh...
我可以吃一些吗
Can I have some of that?
好，当然 我们为你做的
Yeah, sure. We made it for you.
是的
Yeah.
进到那里去
Get in there.
这很不错 是的
This is pretty good. Yeah?
海洋 有没有帮助你做到这一点 哈哈
Did Ocean help you make it? Ha-ha.
她会因为我们没有她而杀了我们
She's gonna kill us for having some without her.
她四岁
She's four.
是的，但是，米基，
Yeah, but, Miki,
她是一个坚强的四人
she's a tough four.
你是个好爸爸，对吧
You're a good dad, huh?
哦，我是说...
Oh, I mean...
..你知道，琳恩对她也很好 惊喜，惊喜
..you know, Lynne's pretty good with her too. Surprise, surprise.
..你知道，琳恩比她和我们在一起时好多了
..you know, Lynne's pretty good Better than she was with us.
你什么时候开始称我们的母亲为“琳恩”的
When did you start calling our mother 'Lynne'?
你什么时候开始的
When did you start
你什么时候见她
When are you gonna see her?
要看
Depends.
她什么时候来看我
When is she gonna see me?
妈的 哦，我的意思是...
Oh, shit. Oh, I meant...
我打算让琳恩明天带海洋去幼儿园
I meant to ask Lynne to take Ocean to preschool tomorrow.
我是想问琳恩我早就出发了
I meant to ask Lynne I've got an early start.
我可以带她
I could take her.
嗯，是同一个地方，对吧
Well, it's the same spot, right?
我不会迷路的
I won't get lost.
呃...
Uh...
好的
OK.
是的 是的
Yeah? Yeah.
嘿，当你想打工的时候，去肉制品厂
Hey, while you're at it, go to the meatworks as well.
他们会有工作 嗯
They'll have jobs going. Mm.
他们会有工作 你可以用我的旧自行车
They'll have jobs going. You can take my old bike.
哇
Whoo!
在你之后
After you.
你要我背你的包吗
Do you want me to carry your bag?
不，谢谢
No, thanks.
好的
OK.
在监狱里是什么感觉
What was it like in prison?
嗯，是这样的，嗯...
Well, it was, um...
这很像开始幼儿园
It was a lot like starting kindergarten.
有很多我不认识的人，
There was a lot of people I didn't really know,
很多关于一切的规则
a lot of rules about everything.
只有我在一天结束时不能回家和家人团聚
Only I couldn't go home to my family at the end of the day.
你难过吗
Were you sad?
是的，我是
Yeah, I was.
我现在很开心
I'm happy now.
那里 是的
There! Yeah.
噢嗨
Oh, hey.
特里来了 你想和特里打个招呼吗
Terry's here. Do you wanna say hi to Terry?
特里来了 是的
Terry's here. Yeah.
来吧，让我们向特里打个招呼
Come on, let's say hi to Terry.
你好 你好
Hi! Hi.
给你 啊，谢谢
Here you are. Ah, thanks.
给你 嘿，伙计 你好吗
Here you are. Hey, mate! How are ya?
好的 嘿，伙计 你好吗
Good. Hey, mate! How are ya?
好的 好的 那很好
Good. Good? That's good.
听着，我想有人从奶奶那里得到了礼物
Look, I think someone got a present from Grandma.
看，我觉得有人哇 它是什么
Look, I think someone Wow! What is it?
你对特里说什么
What do you say to Terry?
谢谢你 别担心朋友
Thank you.  No worries, mate.
我可以打开它吗
Can I open it?
是的，你当然可以 你要在那边打开吗
Yeah, of course you can. Do you wanna open it over there?
是的，你当然可以 很高兴见到你，伙计
Yeah, of course you can. Good to see you, buddy.
哦，你明天晚上去看烟花吗
Oh, are you going to the fireworks tomorrow night?
哦，你会去看烟花吗呃……可能不会
Oh, are you going to the fireworks Uh... Probably not.
我想，对瓦扬来说，这有点太晚了
It's a bit too late for Wayan, I think.
是的
Yeah.
好吧，好吧，我要让海洋是的
OK, well, I was gonna let Ocean Yeah.
好吧，好吧，我要让海洋熬夜一次
OK, well, I was gonna let Ocean stay up just this once
如果你打算
if you were going to.
啊!
Ah!
是的 听起来确实很诱人
Yeah. It does sound tempting.
听着，我……我听到你在说什么，
Look, I...I hear what you're saying,
我很乐意帮助你...
and I would love to help you out...
..但现在对我来说并不是招聘的好时机，你知道吗
..but it's not really a good time for me to be hiring, you know?
我有一个强壮的胃 嗯
I've got a strong stomach. Mm.
正确的 我会做别人不想做的工作
Right? I'll do the jobs no-one else wants to do.
嗯，这很好，这对你下一份工作有好处，
Well, that's good, that's good for you for the next job you go for,
但我有那么多，所以......嗯
but I've got that lot for those, so...mm.
我需要一个工作
I need a job.
好的 这是我假释的一部分
OK. That's part of my parole.
继续，凯夫，给她莱拉的位置
Go on, Kev, give her Laila's spot.
是的，继续，凯夫
Yeah, go on, Kev.
加油，凯夫
Go on, Kev!
其他人：继续，凯夫
OTHERS: Go on, Kev!
加油，凯夫 是的，好吧 好吧
Go on, Kev! Yeah, alright! Alright!
好的，好的，好的
Alright, alright, alright.
那么，你是在给我莱拉的工作吗
So, are you giving me Laila's job?
也许
Maybe.
她做了什么
What did she do?
肠道分类
Gut sorting.
真的吗
Really?
好吧
Alright.
好吧，让我们看看你是由什么组成的
Well, let's see what you're made of.
块是这样的
Block is that way.
来吧，我给你指路
Come on, I'll show you the way.
从这里过来 我们会给你整理
Come through here. We'll sort you out.
使用那个
Use that one.
嗯……嗯……
Um... Uh...
哦 那是莱拉的东西
Oh. That's Laila's stuff.
把它装进袋子里，然后带到难民区
Chuck it in a bag and take it up to the refugee quarters.
现在...
Now...
米基……我
Mik...i.
她怎么了 莱拉
What happened to her? Laila?
凯文雇用他们是因为他可以支付他们所有的费用
Kevin hires them because he can pay them bugger-all.
他持有他们的签证，他们不敢抱怨
Holds their visas over them so they can't complain.
我想她有胆量和愤怒
Reckon she had a gutful and pissed off.
估计她有胆量我会
Reckon she had a gutful I would.
好的，我们车间里见 胡鲁
Alright, see you on the floor. Hooroo.
这是莱拉的工作
This is Laila's job.
伙计，我不能为不在的人保留住工作
Mate, I can't very well keep a job for someone who's not here.
伙计，我不能为不在的人保留住工作 我不能
Mate, I can't very well keep a job OK? I can't.
她的签证不是我的问题
And her visa is not my problem.
这是她的
It's hers.
好吗
OK?
现在回去工作
Now get back to work.
你准备好参观了吗？
Are you ready for the tour?
嗯
Mm.
你确定吗 是的
Are you sure? Yep.
呃……这曾经是机器损坏之前的牛肉车间
Uh... This used to be the beef floor before the machinery carked it.
您大部分时间都会待在这里
You'll be spending most of your time up here.
注意气味
Watch out for the smell.
它真的打动了你
It really hits you.
你说得对吗？
You right?
只是要让你知道，
Just so you know,
那是上面的杀戮箱
that's the kill box up there.
你不该在上面，好吗
You've got no business being up there, OK?
我要你在每次轮班结束时清洗地板
And I want you to wash down the floors at the end of every shift.
戴尔，你能给她看看绳子吗 是的，不用担心
Dale, can you show her the ropes? Yeah, no worries.
- 谢了哥们  - 喂，杀手
- Thanks, mate.  - Oi, killer!
谢了哥们 你接下来要杀谁，嗯
Thanks, mate. Who are you gonna kill next, huh?
当心，否则她会毁了你们所有人
Watch out or she'll gut all of you!
别担心，他们最终会感到无聊
Don't worry, they'll get bored eventually.
你把你的肝脏和心脏扔到那个上面
You throw your liver and hearts down that one.
肺直接穿过
The lungs go straight through.
肠子，肠子往下走
Guts, intestines go down that one.
不是火箭手术
Not rocket surgery.
喂 罗密欧
Oi! Romeo!
拿起你的心，滚蛋
Pick up your heart and fuck off!
你必须像他们中的一员一样 好吧
You've just got to be like one of them. Alright?
你刚到是的 但是如果我不想呢
You've just got to Yep. But what if I don't want to?
那么生活会很糟糕，是的 但是如果我不想呢
Then life's gonna suck pretty hard, Yep. But what if I don't want to?
那么生活会很糟糕，亲爱的
Then life's gonna suck pretty hard, honey.
呃……如果是猪肉的话，我不能吃
Uh... If they are pork, I can't eat them.
它们是香肠 我能告诉你什么
They're sausages. What can I tell you?
你想要它们还是不想要它们 只是土豆泥
Do you want them or not? Just the mash then.
好吧，你适合自己
OK, you suit yourself.
如果你想来，我们大多数晚上下班后都会去酒吧
We go down to the pub most nights after work if you want to come.
答应我，呃...不会对你采取行动
Promise I, uh... won't put the moves on you.
除非你要我
Unless you want me to.
那么，你认为呢 到时候那里见
So, what do you reckon? See you there?
呃...
Uh...
是的，我不……我不这么认为
Yeah, I don't... I don't think so.
你好 这些是，嗯……莱拉的
Hi. These are, um...Laila's.
我不知道该给谁
I don't know who to give this to.
莱拉
Laila?
是的 她在哪
Yeah. Where is she?
是的 呃……我……不知道
Yeah. Uh... I...don't know.
我可以伸出手把旧的拿出来，把新的放进去
I can give a hand to get the old one out and the new one in.
这里
Here.
好的，所以我背靠背有两节课，
Alright, so I've got two lectures back to back,
我想我会留在学习小组
and I thought I'd stay on with the study group.
我会，嗯……我大概会在 11:00 左右到家
I'll, um... I'll be home probably around 11:00.
只要你需要我，我就可以在这里
I can be here as long as you need me.
米基总有一天会来的
Miki's gonna be here at some point.
你最终必须和她谈谈
You have to talk to her eventually.
我不是那个背弃我的人
I'm not the one who turned my back.
安全驾驶
Drive safely.
谢谢
Thanks.
再见 再见
See ya. See ya.
哦，看它——热咖啡冲过来
Oh, watch it - hot coffee coming through.
哦 谢谢你 新鲜的锅
Oh. Thank you. Fresh pot.
哦 谢谢你 是的，嘿，嗯...
Oh. Thank you. Yeah, hey, um...
是的
Yeah?
向我解释你在想什么
Explain to me what you were thinking.
向我解释关于什么
Explain to me About what?
现在聘用她 关于什么
Hiring her now. About what?
现在聘用她 米基
Hiring her now. Miki?
是的 哦
Yeah. Oh!
哦，几周后就没有关系了，是吗
Oh, it won't matter in a couple of weeks, will it?
哦，没关系哦...
Oh, it won't matter Ohh...
我们只需要保持安静哦...
We just have to keep quiet Ohh...
我们只需要保持安静，直到销售结束，
We just have to keep quiet until the sale goes through,
然后是米基和其他人……
and then Miki and the rest of them...
然后Miki ..这不是我们的问题，所以...
and then Miki ..it's not really our problem, so...
嗯
Mm.
然后我们将在飞机上
And then we'll be on a plane.
是的 是的 正确的
Yeah? Yeah! Right?
我们将在飞机上，你，我和Wayan，前往天堂
We'll be on a plane, you, me and Wayan, and heading towards paradise
然后这一切都将在我们身后
and then all of this will be behind us.
爸爸，看
Daddy, look.
哦，哇 哦
Oh, wow! Oh!
安达平塔 是的，还有a pintar
Anda pintar! Yeah, anda pintar.
安达平塔
Anda pintar!
急救柜上锁了
First-aid cabinet's locked.
哦
Oh.
我有你从药房订购的绷带和镇痛药
I've got the bandages and analgesics you ordered from the pharmacy.
得到他 谢谢，康纳
Got him! Thanks, Connor.
干杯 怎么样
Cheers. How's that?!
干杯 你想给我看更多吗
Cheers. Do you want to show me more?
是的 给我看看 来吧
Yeah. Show me. Come on.
为什么 我别无选择
Why? I have no choice.
对不起
Sorry.
交给我
Leave it to me.
我会 我不会提到这一点 我会和他谈谈
I will. I won't mention that. I'll talk to him.
卡车来了
The truck is here!
去 去 去
Go! Go! Go!
她在这里做什么 凯文给了她一份工作
What's she doing here? Kevin gave her a job.
她在这里做什么 是的
What's she doing here?  Yeah.
想稍后回到我的身边吗
Want to come back to mine later?
不，你是在向他们收费，就像他们有海港景色一样
No, you're charging them like they've got harbour views!
如果他们不喜欢，休，他们可以住在别的地方
If they don't like it, Hugh, they can live somewhere else.
你在利用弱势群体
You're taking advantage of vulnerable people.
那正确吗 好的
Is that right? OK.
各位，请稍等 我可以问你一个问题吗
You lot, just hold on a second. Can I ask you a question?
休在这里认为我在利用你
Hugh here thinks I'm taking advantage of you.
真的吗 我在利用你们中的任何一个人吗
Is that true? Am I taking advantage of any of you?
好吧，说出来 如果你有话要说，就说吧
Well, speak up. If you've got something to say, say it.
不挂断
Hang on.
你向我们收取电费，水费
You charge us for electricity, for water.
是的，这些东西不是免费的，伙计 不适合我们任何人
Yes, and those things aren't free, mate. Not for any of us.
是的，这些东西不是免费的，我们没有病假 没有什么
Yes, and those things aren't free, We get no sick days. Nothing.
你认为我可以请一天假吗我们没有病假 没有什么 你认为我可以随时请假吗 你
Do you think I can take a day off We get no sick days. Nothing. Do you think I can take a day off whenever I want? Do you?
你认为我可以请一天假吗我不能
Do you think I can take a day off I can't.
我们所有人都一样
It's the same for all of us!
是这样吗
Is that it?!
好的
Good.
生气 明天见
Piss off! I'll see you tomorrow.
你有什么问题
What is your problem?
它们只是基本条件 你有什么问题
They're just basic conditions. What is your problem?
它们只是基本条件 只是...
They're just basic conditions. Just...
它们只是基本条件 这不关你的事，休
They're just basic conditions. It's none of your business, Hugh.
好的
OK?
请离开
Please go.
在你真的让我生气之前离开，伙计
Leave before you really make me angry, mate.
是的
Yeah.
他妈的做善事
Fucking do-gooder.
哦，你在这儿
Oh, there you are.
你的纱布也快用完了
You're running low on gauze too.
我会回来 你的纱布也快用完了
I'll come back. You're running low on gauze too.
我会回来 好的 谢谢你
I'll come back. OK. Thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
爱你 我也爱你
Love you. Love you too.
你明天不会回来的概率是三比一
There's three-to-one odds going that you won't be back tomorrow.
有三比一的赔率是吗
There's three-to-one odds going Yeah?
你投注哪种方式
Which way are you betting?
哦，我不赌博
Ooh, I don't gamble.
我还有其他恶习
I have other vices.
哦，亚当，看到新鲜的肉了吗
Oi, Adam, seen the fresh meat?
天呐，尼克，闭嘴
Jesus Christ, Nick, shut up.
什么
What?
米基杀了他的妹妹
Miki killed his sister.
没想到你出来了
Didn't think you were ever coming out.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我想说对不起
I want to say sorry and that.
我今天只是在闲逛
I was only mucking around today.
当我开始时，混蛋对我做了
Bastards did it to me when I started.
顺便说一句，我是尼克
I'm Nick, by the way.
你没有打扰我，尼克
You didn't bother me, Nick.
真的吗
Really?
小鸡监狱有那么糟糕吗
Was chick prison that bad?
那么，我可以给你买杯啤酒什么的吗
So, can I buy you a beer or something?
你喝啤酒吗
You drink beer?
是的
Yeah.
是的，我喝啤酒
Yeah, I drink beer.
妈的
Oh, shit.
不挂断 我离开了我的包 妈的
Hang on. I left my bag. Oh, shit.
不挂断 我离开了我的包 我会两秒钟
Hang on. I left my bag. I'll be two secs.
嘿，跟我来，我们走另一条路
Hey, come with me, we'll go out the other way.
尼克 是的 是的，我在这里
Nick. Yeah. Yeah, I'm in here.
你能帮我看看吗 我找不到它
Can you help me look? I can't find it.
我知道感觉很冷，但你不会冻伤或什么都没有
I know it feels cold, but you won't get frostbite or nothing.
我知道感觉很冷，但是
I know it feels cold, but
尼克
Nick?
尼克，开门
Nick, open the door.
你会是对的 只是放松
You'll be right! Just chillax!
尼克
Nick!
哇
Whoo!
尼克，开门
Nick, open the door!
抓住你
Catch ya!
尼克
Nick!
打开他妈的门
Open the fucking door!
尼克
Nick!
打开他妈的门
Open the fucking door!
你好
Hello!
和我们一起吃饭
Eat with us.
嘿，亲爱的 我们吃饭吧，亲爱的
是该去警察局的时候了
不，我告诉过你 不
为什么
这就够了吗 那她会在哪里呢
现在已经好几天了
她是我姐姐 萨利姆
没有上帝，只有真主（亲爱的安拉，给我耐心和平安）
到底是怎么回事
检查这些
我们尊敬的女人
我找到了这些
你姐姐和一个男孩跑了
这与警方无关
他妈的尼克
Fucking Nick.
你好
Hello?
尼克
Nick?
休
Hugh?!
哦
Ohh!
啊 啊
Agh! Agh!
啊
Agh!
不
No!
妈妈
Mum.
从昨晚开始还冷吗
Still cold from last night?
- 我会让你暖和起来，杀手  - 从昨晚开始还冷吗
- I'll warm you up, killer. - Still cold from last night?
我会让你暖和起来，杀手
I'll warm you up, killer.
萨维奇河没有发生过凶杀案
Haven't had a homicide in Savage River
因为她做了她对茉莉所做的事
since she did what she did to Jasmine.
哦
Ohh!
你想再进监狱吗 别客气 有什么要告诉我的吗
You wanna go to prison again? Be my guest. Got something to tell me?
那是……真的吗
Is that...real?
他在哪里 什...什么
Where is he? Wh... What?
他在哪里 因为你，他走了
Where is he? He's gone because of YOU.
你是一个暴力的人 你和我都知道这一点
You're a violent person. You and I both know that.
但我什么也没做
But I didn't do anything.
我会全力以赴，但我什么也没做
I'm gonna be all over you But I didn't do anything.
在我发现之前，我会全力以赴
I'm gonna be all over you till I find out.
英文字幕属红蜂媒体
Captions by Red Bee Media
澳大利亚广播公司版权所有
Copyright Australian Broadcasting Corporation